I wanted to call this video, "Top Five Things That Makes Battlefield 1 Literally Unplayable,"
but the problems I came up with were, at most, mild annoyances,
and I could only come up with three, so...
Battlefield 1's main game type shouldn't be Conquest;
it should be Finding Hitler.
A random soldier gets to be Hitler
and then the other team is supposed to hunt him down.
Then Hitler gets bonus points if he's an asshole in chat or uses hacks.
You know, being a literal Hitler.
Something else I noticed is that many forget that most people didn't die because of the war,
they died because of the Spanish flu.
So another game type should be just you,
lying in the hospital bed, trying not to die.
In Battlefield 2, you would run around without a purpose,
and then the Chinese commander would say...
[speaking Chinese]
...and you would be like, "Yeah! I SHOULD [speaking Chinese].
I should [speaking Chinese] as hard as I can."
But in this game, whatever country you play as, you have this condescending British woman,
and she's like, [British accent:] "We lost objective Dove! That's too bad, i'n'it, mate?"
I just want an angry German commander shouting at me.
We would mess up, and he would shout...
[in German:]
You know, the Germans have a saying:
Every German I've met has said that to me, and I never understood what they meant.
And I still don't, but I feel like it's relevant to the commander thing.
The Allied Powers that lost the most soldiers in World War I were Russia and France,
so it makes sense you can't play as them.
It's already VERY easy to die in this game,
but can we remove other countries?
What has Austria ever done for you?
If you say, "All those Austrian composers," I'm about to blow your mind:
they are...
Korean.
It's not Beethoven; it's /pee-HO-ven/.
I'm not saying they should add Korea to the game; just remove every non-necessary country.
Battlefield 1 should only have United States and Italy.
I know they are on the same side, but it's not like the game is historically accurate, anyways.
Actually, remove Italy, too.
Make it America versus America.
It's kind of topical, considering recent events.